A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1968-1969
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1968-1969
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.721
This collection consists of 38,400 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 20 July 1972.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
Contents List
- General Files, 1968-1969
  - "A - Am" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - "An - Az" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Academic Deans 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Adams Papers 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Admissions - General 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Admissions - Reports 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Admissions - Applicants, "A - Z" 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Panel on ROTC Affairs 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Air Force Academy - Board of Visitors 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Air Force and Air Force ROTC 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - General 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Chapters Planned 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Alumni Day 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Alumni 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Fund, University of Virginia 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Medical 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association - Alumni News 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association - Alumni Recognition 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association - Maryland Chapter 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association - New York Chapter 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association - Norfolk-Portsmouth Chapter 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association - Philadelphia Chapter 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association - Washington Chapter 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association - Richmond 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Board of Trustees 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - American Association of University Professors 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - American Council on Education -2 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - American Council on Education - "Educational Record (Spring 1969)" 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - American Council on Education (1) 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - American Council on Education - Board of Directors 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - American Council on Education - Publications 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Ancient Languages 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Annual Reports 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Applications for Positions, "A - Z" 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Architecture - General 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Architecture - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Army - General 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Army - Judge Advocate General's (J.A.G.) School 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Army - J.A.G. School Building 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Army - ROTC (Military Science) 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Art 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Art - Graduate Institute of History of Art 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Association of American Colleges 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Association of American Universities 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Tenth Commonwealth Universities; Australia 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Astronomy 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - ACC 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - Finances 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - ACC 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - NCAA 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - 3 -2 - 2 Committee 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Invitations to Games 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football: Purdue Game, 21 September 1968 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football: V. M. I. Game, 26 September 1968 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football: Davidson Game, 5 October 1968 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football: S. C. Game, 2 November 1968 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football: Tulane Game, 16 November 1968 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Athletics - Football: Maryland Game, 23 November 1968 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Athletics - Rowing Team 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Athletics - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Atomic Energy - Annual Report to Congress of the Atomic Energy Commission for 19681968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Atomic Energy - Fundamental Nuclear Energy Research - 19681968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Atomic Energy Commission 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Audit Reports 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - "B - Bm" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - "Bn - Bz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - Biology - Blandy Farm 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Biology - General 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Biology - Mountain Lake 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Budget Office - Director's Office 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Budget Office - Capital Outlay 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Budget Office - Budget Exhibit for the University of Virginia and the University of Virginia Hospital Division1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Budget Office - Miscellaneous Information 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Budget Office - New Positions Needed 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Budget Office - Requests 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds - General 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds - Progress Reports 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Building Program 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Bureau of Population and Economic Research 1968-1969 (Box 13)
  - Bursar 1968-1969 (Box 13)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education 1968-1969 (Box 13)
  - "Ca - Ck" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 13)
  - "Cl - Cz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Calendar of Events 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Catholic Center 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - University of Virginia 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Cavalier Daily 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Center For Advanced Studies - University Science Development Proposal for a Supplemental Grant(1) 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Center For Advanced Studies - University Science Development Proposal for a Supplemental Grant(2) 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Center For Advanced Studies - A Proposal For a Cooperative Foreign Fellowship Program1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - General 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Chemistry - General 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Chemistry - Chemistry Building 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Children's Rehabilitation Center 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Civil Defense 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - Civil Rights 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - Classics 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - Clinch Valley College - Building Program 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - Clinch Valley College - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - College Entrance Examination Board 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - Commerce - General 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - Commerce - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - Administrative Committee 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - AD HOC - Advisory Committee on Personnel Practices 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - AD HOC - Clinical Psychology 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - AD HOC - Fine Arts Library 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - AD HOC - Research Development and Public Service 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - AD HOC - Committee or Student Car Regulations 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Admissions 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Architectural Advisory Committee 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Athletic Advisory 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Calendar and Scheduling 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Catalogue 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Chapel 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Communications 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Computer-Science Center 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Data-Processing 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Foreign Students 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Fraternities 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Fulbright Grants 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Future of the University 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Graduate Awards and Recruiting 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Graduate 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Gwathmey Award 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Housing 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Institutional Analysis 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Lectures -Special 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Committee - Lectures - Page-Barbour and Richard 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Library 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Master Plan 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Names 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - National Medal of Science 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Objects of Art 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Patents 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Processions 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Public Occasions 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Radiation Safety 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Registration 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Research 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Research and Sponsored Programs 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Rhodes Scholarships 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - ROTC Affairs 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Loans, and Employment Fellowships 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Security and General Safety 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Student Activities 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Summer Grants 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Traffic Control 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - University Colleges 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - University Committee on Students 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - University Press (folder empty) 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - University Union 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Virginia Quarterly Review Advisory 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Virginia Status of University Students 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Committee - Wilson Gee Institute for Research in the Social Sciences 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Special Committee - Academic Legislation 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Special Committee - Addition - Children's Rehabilitation Center 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Special Committee - Report of Committee on Admission of Women (Woody Report) 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - Admission, Women to the College of Arts and Sciences 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - Children's Rehabilitation Center 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - New Buildings at Clinch Valley College 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - Education, Dean of 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - Selection, Dean of Faculty of Arts and Sciences and Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - Faculty Handbook 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - Fine Arts Center 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - George Mason Advisory 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - George Mason College, Chancellor for 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Special Committee - G. M. C. Master Plan Review 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - George Mason College Student Union Building 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Heating Plant Alterations and Additions 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Medical Center Communications Building, Medical Library 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Orientation 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Patrick Henry Advisory 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Religious Organizational Use of University Facilities 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Sesquicentennial Associate Selection Committee 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Seven Society Award 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Social Needs and Facilities 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Tree 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - University Committee on Committees 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Special Committee - Vivarium 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Community Colleges 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Comptroller 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Computer Center 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Cooper, Weldon 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Copely Hill - Married Student Housing 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Clinch Valley College - General 1968-1969 (Box 21)
  - Council of Presidents Special Committee on Salaries 1968-1969 (Box 21)
  - Council of Presidents 1968-1969 (Box 21)
  - Council of Southern Universities 1968-1969 (Box 21)
  - "Da - De" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 21)
  - "Df - Dz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 21)
  - Danforth Foundation 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Darlington School, Board of Trustees 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Deans Luncheons 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Degrees 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Demonstrations 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Development and Public Affairs (Mr. Hobbs) 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Ditchley Foundation 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - "E" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Economics 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Education - General 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Education - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Education Research, Division of 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Education - Rehabilitation Center 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Educational T. V. 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Endowment Fund 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Emeriti 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - "F" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Faculty Signatures endorsing the President 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Engineering and Applied Science - General 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - English 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Engineering and Buildings (Hamner) 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Enrollment 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - General Faculty 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Faculty Orientation and Reception 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - General 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Personnel, "A - M" 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Personnel, "N - Z" 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Committee of 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Committee on Education Policy and the Budget 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Department Chairman 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Federal Executive Institute 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Federal Legislation 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - General 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Cross 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Dupont Regional 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Fulbright 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Hoxton 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Love 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Rhodes 1968-1969 (Box 27)
  - Finals 1969 1968-1969 (Box 28)
  - Financial Aid to Students, Office of 1968-1969 (Box 28)
  - Ford Foundation 1968-1969 (Box 29)
  - Foreign Student Advisor 1968-1969 (Box 29)
  - Founder's Day 1969 1968-1969 (Box 29)
  - "G" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 30)
  - Garden Club of Virginia, 1968-1969 1968-1969 (Box 30)
  - Garden Club of Virginia, 1966-1967 1968-1969 (Box 30)
  - Garden Club of Virginia, 1965-1966 1968-1969 (Box 30)
  - Garden Club of Virginia, 1964-1965 1968-1969 (Box 30)
  - General Assembly (See also Legislative Program) 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - General 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Branches Proposed 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Central Virginia Center 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Branch 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Hampton Roads Center 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Hampton Roads Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Lynchburg Branch 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Lynchburg Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center (Book) 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center (Folder) 1968-1969 (Box 31)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Patrick Henry Branch 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Patrick Henry Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Richmond Center 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Richmond Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Roanoke Center 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Roanoke Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Southwest Virginia Center 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - General Studies - Southwest Virginia Center Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - Geography 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - Geology 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - George Mason College - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - George Mason College - Building Program 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - George Mason College - Monthly Reports 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - George mason College - General 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - Germanic and Slavic Languages 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - Gift and Grants Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 33)
  - Gifts and Grants (4) 1968-1969 (Box 33)
  - Gifts and Grants (3) 1968-1969 (Box 34)
  - Gifts and Grants (2) 1968-1969 (Box 34)
  - Gifts and Grants (1) 1968-1969 (Box 35)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1968-1969 (Box 35)
  - Governor's Office 1968-1969 (Box 35)
  - Travel Regulations 1968-1969 (Box 35)
  - Governor's Visit and Advisory Board, 29 April 1969 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Research and Development Facilities and Personnel, Virginia 1968(book) 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Graduate - Graduate Programs 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Graduate Business - Sponsors 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Grants-in-Aid for Students with Culturally Limited Backgrounds 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Graphics Department 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Guggenheim Foundation 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - "Ha - Hh" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 37)
  - "Hi - Hz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 37)
  - Harvard Graduate Society Council 1968-1969 (Box 37)
  - Higher Education Amendments of 1968 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act 1962 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act 1965 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act Title I 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act Title II 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act Title III 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act Title IV 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act Title V 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act Title VI 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Higher Education Act Title VIII 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Highway Department 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - History 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Honors System and Honor Committee 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Honors Program 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Housing 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - Housing, Married Students (see Copely Hill) 1968-1969 (Box 38)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 39)
  - International Association of Chiefs of Police - Staff Assistance Report(Book) 1968-1969 (Box 39)
  - Informational Services (see also Public Relations and Development) 1968-1969 (Box 39)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs 1968-1969 (Box 39)
  - Institute of Government 1968-1969 (Box 39)
  - Institute of International Education 1968-1969 (Box 39)
  - Institutional Analysis (Papers) 1968-1969 (Box 40)
  - Institutional Analysis (Folder) 1968-1969 (Box 40)
  - Institutional Self-Study 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "A" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "B" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "C" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "D" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "E" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "F" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "G" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "H" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "I" 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Invitations - "J" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "K" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "L" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "M" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "N" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "O" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "P" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "Q" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "R" 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Invitations - "S" 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - Invitations - "T" 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - Invitations - "U" 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - Invitations - "V" 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - Invitations - "W" 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - Invitations - "X" 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - Invitations - "Y" 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - Invitations - "Z" 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - "J" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 44)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation (see also Founder's Day) 1968-1969 (Box 44)
  - Jefferson Society 1968-1969 (Box 44)
  - Judiciary Committee 1968-1969 (Box 44)
  - Judge Advocate General's (J. A. G.) School 1968-1969 (Box 44)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 44)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation (see also Founder' s Day) 1968-1969 (Box 45)
  - Jefferson Society 1968-1969 (Box 45)
  - Judiciary Committee 1968-1969 (Box 45)
  - Judge Advocate General's School 1968-1969 (Box 45)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 45)
  - Law - General 1968-1969 (Box 46)
  - Law - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 46)
  - Law - Reading Guide, December 19681968-1969 (Box 46)
  - Lectures 1968-1969 (Box 46)
  - Legal - General 1968-1969 (Box 46)
  - Legal Advisor 1968-1969 (Box 46)
  - Legal - Estates 1968-1969 (Box 46)
  - Library - General 1968-1969 (Box 47)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 47)
  - McGregor Fund 1968-1969 (Box 47)
  - McIntire Fund (see legal file) 1968-1969 (Box 47)
  - "Ma - Me" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 48)
  - "Mi - Mz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 48)
  - Mariner's Museum - Phase "A" Study for the Mariner's Museum, Newport News, Virginia1968-1969 (Box 48)
  - Mariner's Museum - Appraisal Report on Market Value for Balance Sheet Purposes of Real Estate Located in the Newport News Area Owned by the Mariner's Museum1968-1969 (Box 48)
  - Mariner's Museum - General 1968-1969 (Box 48)
  - Marine Science 1968-1969 (Box 48)
  - Markle Foundation 1968-1969 (Box 50)
  - Mary Washington College - General 1968-1969 (Box 50)
  - Mary Washington College - Building Program 1968-1969 (Box 51)
  - Mary Washington College - Financial 1968-1969 (Box 51)
  - Mary Washington College - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 51)
  - Mathematics 1968-1969 (Box 51)
  - Medical Center - General 1968-1969 (Box 51)
  - Medical School - Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 51)
  - Medical Center - Building Program 1968-1969 (Box 51)
  - Medical Center - Hospital 1968-1969 (Box 51)
  - Medical Center - Monthly Statistical Reports 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Medical Center - Nursing 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Medical Center - Operating Budget and Reports 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Medical Center - Rehabilitation and Training Center (see Rehabilitation Center) 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Medical Center - Reports on Current Operations 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Medical Center - Finances 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Medical Center - Nursing - Curricula, reports, etc. (Mr. Berkeley's copy) 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Medical Center - Nursing Personnel 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Medical Center - Rehabilitation and Training Center 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Mental Health 1968-1969 (Box 52)
  - Miller Bill 1968-1969 (Box 53)
  - Miller Bill 1968-1969 (Box 53)
  - Monroe, James - Monroe Foundation and Library 1968-1969 (Box 53)
  - Mountain Lake Conference 1968-1969 (Box 53)
  - Music 1968-1969 (Box 54)
  - "Na" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 54)
  - "Nb - Nz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 54)
  - NASA (see also VARC) 1968-1969 (Box 55)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges 1968-1969 (Box 55)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Public Higher Education and the State Legislature: Changing Relationships1968-1969 (Box 56)
  - State Universities and Public Affairs 1968-1969 (Box 56)
  - 81st Annual Convention, 12-15 November 1967 1968-1969 (Box 56)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - International Letters 1968-1969 (Box 56)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Circular Letters 1968-1969 (Box 56)